In the province of Trois, there is
a town of lakes and glass: Seize.
My name is Kanata Sorami and
I aspire to become a trumpeter.
I've come to the fortress of the 1121st Platoon
and have met many people there.
First, the gunner: Kureha.
She's younger than me, but she enlisted before me,
so she's both my senior and like a little sister, sort of.
She was acting a bit cold at first,
but we're great friends now.
Next is the pilot and mechanic, Noel.
She was pretty taciturn
so at first I thought she didn't like me,
but she just doesn't talk much
and is actually a very kind girl.
She's also very smart, always reading difficult books
and does maintenance on the Takemikazuchi.
Oh, right, I forgot about the commander!
Commander Filicia Heideman.
She's like a mother or big sister to us.
Her cooking is great and we all really look up to her.
And the person I admire the most:
Rio, also a trumpeter.
She had to leave the Time-Telling Fortress
for a while due to family matters,
but she was able to come back for the time being.
Rio returning was like finding a missing note.
The story of the 1121st Platoon
can play out once again.
Beautiful things, sullied things...
hardships but fun times, too.
Happiness, and also pain...
We, the maidens of the fortress
are performing as a quintet again, in a far-off corner of the world.
One day, as the curtain is raised...